Smashing party, Your Majesty.
这聚会棒极了 女王陛下
But now, I'm afraid Sherman and I must be...
但是现在 恐怕舍曼和我必须...
Sherman? Sherman?
舍曼 舍曼
Sherman!
舍曼
Sherman?
Sherman! Here, Sherman.
舍曼 这里 舍曼
Hey, Mr. Peabody.
嘿 皮博迪先生
What are you doing in here?
你在这儿干嘛呢
Trying these other cakes.
尝尝其他的蛋糕
There's one in here with whipped cream and strawberries that's...
这边有一个是生奶油和草莓做的...
pretty fantastic!
超好吃
Sherman，don't you remember why I told you to stay
舍曼，你难道不记得我告诉你的
close to me during the French Revolution?
在法国革命期间要一直呆在我身边吗
Because after the French Revolution...
因为在法国革命之后...
- it was gonna rain?  - Close.
- 就要下雨了是吗  - 有点接近
I said, "After the French Revolution comes...
我说 "在法国革命开始后...
the Reign of Terror!"
就是腥风血雨"